<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Unknown on Datasheet for Game Commentary Datasets</title><link>https://ZzZqr.github.io/AIGGC-datasheet/tags/unknown/</link><description>Recent content in Unknown on Datasheet for Game Commentary Datasets</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.147.2</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ZzZqr.github.io/AIGGC-datasheet/tags/unknown/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Extraction of Strong and Weak Regions of Cricket Batsman through Text-Commentary Analysis</title><link>https://ZzZqr.github.io/AIGGC-datasheet/datasets/extraction-of-strong-and-weak-regions-of-cricket-batsman-through-text-commentary-analysis/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ZzZqr.github.io/AIGGC-datasheet/datasets/extraction-of-strong-and-weak-regions-of-cricket-batsman-through-text-commentary-analysis/</guid><description>&lt;p>Cricket is a famous game in the world where many metrics are introduced and being used to help the coaches and umpires to solve the critical problems. Though different statistics are used to quantify the player&amp;rsquo;s performance based on strike rate, average or for ranking, prediction, and optimal team selection. There is not any effective method to measure the strong and weak regions of a batsman in cricket. In this paper, a text mining method is presented to extract either the strong shot selection points that are frequent for scoring or weak shot regions that seem tough for a batsman to play. Also, a mechanism is put forward to calculate the region-wise strike rate of an individual batsman. To achieve the objectives, the T20 cricket text commentary is being used for this purpose which is available on the espncricinfo website. The proposed method can be helpful for coaches and players to know the strong or weak regions where the batsman feels ease or difficulty to play, respectively. Moreover, the opponent bowlers can also use this method to plan the area where to bowl to each batsman.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>