<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Basketball on Datasheet for Game Commentary Datasets</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/AIGGC-datasheet/tags/basketball/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Basketball on Datasheet for Game Commentary Datasets</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/AIGGC-datasheet/tags/basketball/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>A Descriptive Basketball Highlight Dataset for Automatic Commentary Generation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/AIGGC-datasheet/datasets/a-descriptive-basketball-highlight-dataset-for-automatic-commentary-generation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/AIGGC-datasheet/datasets/a-descriptive-basketball-highlight-dataset-for-automatic-commentary-generation/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The emergence of video captioning makes it possible to automatically generate natural language description for a given video. However, generating detailed video descriptions that incorporate domain-specific information remains an unsolved challenge, holding significant research and application value, particularly in domains such as sports commentary generation. Moreover, sports event commentary goes beyond being a mere game report, it involves entertaining, metaphorical, and emotional descriptions. To promote the field of sports commentary automatic generation, in this paper, we introduce a novel dataset, the Basketball Highlight Commentary (BH-Commentary), comprising approximately 4K basketball highlight videos with groundtruth commentaries from professional commentators. In addition, we propose an end-to-end framework as a benchmark for basketball highlight commentary generation task, in which a lightweight and effective prompt strategy is designed to enhance alignment fusion among visual and textual features. Experimental results on the BH-Commentary dataset demonstrate the validity of the dataset and the effectiveness of the proposed benchmark for sports highlight commentary generation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
