<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>FPS on Datasheet for Game Commentary Datasets</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/AIGGC-datasheet/tags/fps/</link>
    <description>Recent content in FPS on Datasheet for Game Commentary Datasets</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/AIGGC-datasheet/tags/fps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Conceptual Representation and Evaluation of an FPS Game Commentary Ger</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/AIGGC-datasheet/datasets/conceptual-representation-and-evaluation-of-an-fps-game-commentary-generator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/AIGGC-datasheet/datasets/conceptual-representation-and-evaluation-of-an-fps-game-commentary-generator/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Playing video games has been popular across all the age limits of modern society. In the beginning, it was limited among the younger community and it was just a hobby limited to individuals. Even though the majority of society sees video gaming as having a negative impact on society, this modern industry acts a significant role in healing the present competitive, stressful society. Game commentary has played a major role in the domain of competitive ESports. A proper game commentary is beneficial to both players and the audience. The aim of this project is to analyze the gameplays to produce a commentary track while balancing the contributing factors, color commentary, and play-by-play commentary. The project consists of three modules that perform the study in three perspectives: 1. Word sets related to action, spatial, temporal, and statistical information, 2. Word sets related to color commentary, 3. Word sets related to play-by-play commentary. In each module, a game commentary is generated using only the word sets related to that module. For evaluation, the similarity between the human commentary and the generated commentaries individually will be calculated.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
