<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Chess on Datasheet for Game Commentary Datasets</title><link>https://ZzZqr.github.io/AIGGC-datasheet/tags/chess/</link><description>Recent content in Chess on Datasheet for Game Commentary Datasets</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.147.2</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ZzZqr.github.io/AIGGC-datasheet/tags/chess/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Aspect-based Sentiment Evaluation of Chess Moves (ASSESS): an NLP-based Method for Evaluating Chess Strategies from Textbooks</title><link>https://ZzZqr.github.io/AIGGC-datasheet/datasets/aspect-based-sentiment-evaluation-of-chess-moves-assess-an-nlp-based-method-for-evaluating-chess-strategies-from-textbooks/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ZzZqr.github.io/AIGGC-datasheet/datasets/aspect-based-sentiment-evaluation-of-chess-moves-assess-an-nlp-based-method-for-evaluating-chess-strategies-from-textbooks/</guid><description>&lt;p>The chess domain is well-suited for creating an artificial intelligence (AI) system that mimics real-world challenges, including decision-making. Throughout the years, minimal attention has been paid to investigating insights derived from unstructured chess data sources. In this study, we examine the complicated relationships between multiple referenced moves in a chess-teaching textbook, and propose a novel method designed to encapsulate chess knowledge derived from move-action phrases. This study investigates the feasibility of using a modified sentiment analysis method as a means for evaluating chess moves based on text. Our proposed Aspect-Based Sentiment Analysis (ABSA) method represents an advancement in evaluating the sentiment associated with referenced chess moves. By extracting insights from move-action phrases, our approach aims to provide a more fine-grained and contextually aware {\textquoteleft}chess move&amp;rsquo;-based sentiment classification. Through empirical experiments and analysis, we evaluate the performance of our fine-tuned ABSA model, presenting results that confirm the efficiency of our approach in advancing aspect-based sentiment classification within the chess domain. This research contributes to the area of game-playing by machines and shows the practical applicability of leveraging NLP techniques to understand the context of strategic games. Keywords: Natural Language Processing, Chess, Aspect-based Sentiment Analysis (ABSA), Chess Move Evaluation.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Learning to Generate Move-by-Move Commentary for Chess Games from Large-Scale Social Forum Data</title><link>https://ZzZqr.github.io/AIGGC-datasheet/datasets/learning-to-generate-move-by-move-commentary-for-chess-games-from-large-scale-social-forum-data/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ZzZqr.github.io/AIGGC-datasheet/datasets/learning-to-generate-move-by-move-commentary-for-chess-games-from-large-scale-social-forum-data/</guid><description>&lt;p>This paper examines the problem of generating natural language descriptions of chess games. We introduce a new large-scale chess commentary dataset and propose methods to generate commentary for individual moves in a chess game. The introduced dataset consists of more than 298K chess move-commentary pairs across 11K chess games. We highlight how this task poses unique research challenges in natural language generation: the data contain a large variety of styles of commentary and frequently depend on pragmatic context. We benchmark various baselines and propose an end-to-end trainable neural model which takes into account multiple pragmatic aspects of the game state that may be commented upon to describe a given chess move. Through a human study on predictions for a subset of the data which deals with direct move descriptions, we observe that outputs from our models are rated similar to ground truth commentary texts in terms of correctness and fluency.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>SentiMATE: Learning to play Chess through Natural Language Processing</title><link>https://ZzZqr.github.io/AIGGC-datasheet/datasets/sentimate-learning-to-play-chess-through-natural-language-processing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ZzZqr.github.io/AIGGC-datasheet/datasets/sentimate-learning-to-play-chess-through-natural-language-processing/</guid><description>&lt;p>We present SentiMATE, a novel end-to-end Deep Learning model for Chess, employing Natural Language Processing that aims to learn an effective evaluation function assessing move quality. This function is pre-trained on the sentiment of commentary associated with the training moves and is used to guide and optimize the agent&amp;rsquo;s game-playing decision making. The contributions of this research are three-fold: we build and put forward both a classifier which extracts commentary describing the quality of Chess moves in vast commentary datasets, and a Sentiment Analysis model trained on Chess commentary to accurately predict the quality of said moves, to then use those predictions to evaluate the optimal next move of a Chess agent. Both classifiers achieve over 90 which evaluates Chess moves based on a pre-trained sentiment evaluation function. Our results exhibit strong evidence to support our initial hypothesis - &amp;ldquo;Can Natural Language Processing be used to train a novel and sample efficient evaluation function in Chess Engines?&amp;rdquo; - as we integrate our evaluation function into modern Chess engines and play against agents with traditional Chess move evaluation functions, beating both random agents and a DeepChess implementation at a level-one search depth - representing the number of moves a traditional Chess agent (employing the alpha-beta search algorithm) looks ahead in order to evaluate a given chess state.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>