<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Chess on Datasheet for Game Commentary Datasets</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/AIGGC-datasheet/tags/chess/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Chess on Datasheet for Game Commentary Datasets</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/AIGGC-datasheet/tags/chess/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Aspect-based Sentiment Evaluation of Chess Moves (ASSESS): an NLP-based Method for Evaluating Chess Strategies from Textbooks</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/AIGGC-datasheet/datasets/aspect-based-sentiment-evaluation-of-chess-moves-assess-an-nlp-based-method-for-evaluating-chess-strategies-from-textbooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/AIGGC-datasheet/datasets/aspect-based-sentiment-evaluation-of-chess-moves-assess-an-nlp-based-method-for-evaluating-chess-strategies-from-textbooks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The chess domain is well-suited for creating an artificial intelligence (AI) system that mimics real-world challenges, including decision-making. Throughout the years, minimal attention has been paid to investigating insights derived from unstructured chess data sources. In this study, we examine the complicated relationships between multiple referenced moves in a chess-teaching textbook, and propose a novel method designed to encapsulate chess knowledge derived from move-action phrases. This study investigates the feasibility of using a modified sentiment analysis method as a means for evaluating chess moves based on text. Our proposed Aspect-Based Sentiment Analysis (ABSA) method represents an advancement in evaluating the sentiment associated with referenced chess moves. By extracting insights from move-action phrases, our approach aims to provide a more fine-grained and contextually aware {\textquoteleft}chess move&amp;rsquo;-based sentiment classification. Through empirical experiments and analysis, we evaluate the performance of our fine-tuned ABSA model, presenting results that confirm the efficiency of our approach in advancing aspect-based sentiment classification within the chess domain. This research contributes to the area of game-playing by machines and shows the practical applicability of leveraging NLP techniques to understand the context of strategic games. Keywords: Natural Language Processing, Chess, Aspect-based Sentiment Analysis (ABSA), Chess Move Evaluation.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
