<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Shogi on Datasheet for Game Commentary Datasets</title><link>https://ZzZqr.github.io/AIGGC-datasheet/tags/shogi/</link><description>Recent content in Shogi on Datasheet for Game Commentary Datasets</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.147.2</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://ZzZqr.github.io/AIGGC-datasheet/tags/shogi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Japanese Chess Commentary Corpus</title><link>https://ZzZqr.github.io/AIGGC-datasheet/datasets/a-japanese-chess-commentary-corpus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ZzZqr.github.io/AIGGC-datasheet/datasets/a-japanese-chess-commentary-corpus/</guid><description>&lt;p>In recent years there has been a surge of interest in the natural language prosessing related to the real world, such as symbol grounding, language generation, and nonlinguistic data search by natural language queries. In order to concentrate on language ambiguities, we propose to use a well-defined {\textquotedblleft}real world,{\textquotedblright} that is game states. We built a corpus consisting of pairs of sentences and a game state. The game we focus on is shogi (Japanese chess). We collected 742,286 commentary sentences in Japanese. They are spontaneously generated contrary to natural language annotations in many image datasets provided by human workers on Amazon Mechanical Turk. We defined domain specific named entities and we segmented 2,508 sentences into words manually and annotated each word with a named entity tag. We describe a detailed definition of named entities and show some statistics of our game commentary corpus. We also show the results of the experiments of word segmentation and named entity recognition. The accuracies are as high as those on general domain texts indicating that we are ready to tackle various new problems related to the real world.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Annotating Event Appearance for Japanese Chess Commentary Corpus</title><link>https://ZzZqr.github.io/AIGGC-datasheet/datasets/annotating-event-appearance-for-japanese-chess-commentary-corpus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ZzZqr.github.io/AIGGC-datasheet/datasets/annotating-event-appearance-for-japanese-chess-commentary-corpus/</guid><description>&lt;p>In recent years, there has been a surge of interest in natural language processing related to the real world, such as symbol grounding, language generation, and non-linguistic data search by natural language queries. Researchers usually collect pairs of text and non-text data for research. However, the text and non-text data are not always a {\textquotedblleft}true{\textquotedblright} pair. We focused on the shogi (Japanese chess) commentaries, which are accompanied by game states as a well-defined {\textquotedblleft}real world{\textquotedblright}. For analyzing and processing texts accurately, considering only the given states is insufficient, and we must consider the relationship between texts and the real world. In this paper, we propose {\textquotedblleft}Event Appearance{\textquotedblright} labels that show the relationship between events mentioned in texts and those happening in the real world. Our event appearance label set consists of temporal relation, appearance probability, and evidence of the event. Statistics of the annotated corpus and the experimental result show that there exists temporal relation which skillful annotators realize in common. However, it is hard to predict the relationship only by considering the given states.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Annotating Modality Expressions and Event Factuality for a{Japanese Chess Commentary Corpus</title><link>https://ZzZqr.github.io/AIGGC-datasheet/datasets/annotating-modality-expressions-and-event-factuality-for-a-japanese-chess-commentary-corpus/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ZzZqr.github.io/AIGGC-datasheet/datasets/annotating-modality-expressions-and-event-factuality-for-a-japanese-chess-commentary-corpus/</guid><description>&lt;p>In recent years, there has been a surge of interest in the natural language processing related to the real world, such as symbol grounding, language generation, and nonlinguistic data search by natural language queries. We argue that shogi (Japanese chess) commentaries, which are accompanied by game states, are an interesting testbed for these tasks. A commentator refers not only to the current board state but to past and future moves, and yet such references can be grounded in the game tree, possibly with the help of modern game-tree search algorithms. For this reason, we previously collected shogi commentaries together with board states and have been developing a game commentary generator. In this paper, we augment the corpus with manual annotation of modality expressions and event factuality. The annotated corpus includes 1,622 modality expressions, 5,014 event class tags and 3,092 factuality tags. It can be used to train a computer to identify words and phrases that signal factuality and to determine events with the said factuality, paving the way for grounding possible and counterfactual states.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Learning a game commentary generator with grounded move expressions</title><link>https://ZzZqr.github.io/AIGGC-datasheet/datasets/learning-a-game-commentary-generator-with-grounded-move-expressions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ZzZqr.github.io/AIGGC-datasheet/datasets/learning-a-game-commentary-generator-with-grounded-move-expressions/</guid><description>&lt;p>This paper describes a machine learning-based approach for generating natural language comments on Shogi games. We generate comments by using a discriminative language model trained with a large amount of Shogi game records and comments made by human experts. Central to our method is accurate mapping of move expressions appearing in experts&amp;rsquo; comments to game states (i.e. positions) of Shogi, because the discriminative language model is trained with textual expressions paired with corresponding Shogi positions. We describe how such mapping can be performed by using evaluation information obtained from a Shogi program. Experimental results show that we can actually generate helpful comments for some positions.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>